{
  "response_code": 0,
  "results": [
    {
      "category": "Sports%3A%20General",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "question": "Who%20won%20the%20NBA%20Most%20Valuable%20Player%20(MVP)%20award%20in%202020%3F",
      "correct_answer": "Giannis%20Antetokounmpo",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "LeBron%20James",
        "James%20Harden",
        "Kevin%20Durant"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "Sports%3A%20General",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "question": "Which%20NFL%20team%20has%20won%20the%20most%20Super%20Bowl%20titles%3F",
      "correct_answer": "Pittsburgh%20Steelers",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "New%20England%20Patriots",
        "San%20Francisco%2049ers",
        "Dallas%20Cowboys"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "Sports%3A%20General",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "question": "Who%20won%20the%20FIFA%20World%20Cup%20in%202014%3F",
      "correct_answer": "Germany",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Brazil",
        "Argentina",
        "Spain"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "Sports%3A%20General",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "question": "Which%20NBA%20player%20holds%20the%20record%20for%20the%20most%20points%20scored%20in%20a%20single%20game%3F",
      "correct_answer": "Wilt%20Chamberlain",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Kobe%20Bryant",
        "Michael%20Jordan",
        "LeBron%20James"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "Sports%3A%20General",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "question": "In%20which%20year%20was%20the%20first%20FIFA%20World%20Cup%20held%3F",
      "correct_answer": "1930",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "1926",
        "1934",
        "1950"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "Sports%3A%20General",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "question": "Which%20NFL%20quarterback%20has%20won%20the%20most%20Super%20Bowl%20MVP%20awards%3F",
      "correct_answer": "Tom%20Brady",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Joe%20Montana",
        "Terry%20Bradshaw",
        "Peyton%20Manning"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "Sports%3A%20General",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "question": "Who%20won%20the%20NBA%20Rookie%20of%20the%20Year%20award%20in%202021%3F",
      "correct_answer": "LaMelo%20Ball",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Anthony%20Edwards",
        "Tyrese%20Haliburton",
        "James%20Wiseman"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "Sports%3A%20General",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "question": "Which%20country%20hosted%20the%20FIFA%20World%20Cup%20in%202022%3F",
      "correct_answer": "Qatar",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Russia",
        "Germany",
        "Brazil"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "Sports%3A%20General",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "question": "Which%20NFL%20team%20holds%20the%20record%20for%20most%20consecutive%20Super%20Bowl%20appearances%3F",
      "correct_answer": "Buffalo%20Bills",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "New%20England%20Patriots",
        "Miami%20Dolphins",
        "Dallas%20Cowboys"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "Sports%3A%20General",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "question": "Who%20is%20the%20all-time%20leading%20rusher%20in%20NFL%20history%3F",
      "correct_answer": "Emmitt%20Smith",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Walter%20Payton",
        "Barry%20Sanders",
        "Adrian%20Peterson"
      ]
    }
  ]
}
